backpacking-tips-asia.com 2012-04-27

# Backpacking Privacy Policy | Backpacking Tips Asia |

* * *

* * *

### "Your Privacy is Important" 

I recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information I receive and collect when you browse through Backpacking Tips Asia.com, as well as some of the steps I take to safeguard information. I hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with me. 

Backpacking Tips Asia.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all its operations. Likewise, I am dedicated to protecting my customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on my website. 

**Personal Information**

Backpacking Tips Asia collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to this website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. 

This information is collected if you request information from me, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join my newsletter list or request some other service or information from Backpacking Tips Asia.com. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of my website, notify my visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. 

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in my files. If I make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information I will inform you by placing a notice on my site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

I may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable my systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of my site's services, a cookie enables Backpacking Tips Asia.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. 

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site. 

I may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on my web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give me is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on my web site. 

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to my users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with my site, should you so choose. 

**Search Box**

The search box on this web site ("Search Box") is powered by Google Inc. ("Google"). You acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy (located at [Google Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. I operate my site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

**Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, I may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. I use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about my user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

**Release of Information**

If Backpacking Tips Asia.com is sold, the information I have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in my site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through my website of that change in control and practices, and I will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of me. 

**How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

I provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of my commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through my website and would like that information deleted from my records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link to use my [Contact Me page.](http://www.backpacking-tips-asia.com/contact-me.html)

**Updates and Effective Date**

Backpacking Tips Asia.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in my privacy practices, I will indicate on my site that my privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information I collect and how I use it. 

**Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to Backpacking Tips Asia.com's Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. 

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. 

Amanda 

_www.backpacking-tips-asia.com_

* * *

**You're done with Privacy Policy**

* * *

[Return from Privacy Policy to Backpacking Tips Asia Homepage.](http://www.backpacking-tips-asia.com/index.html)

* * *
